{"experimentVersion":"mapping_practice","participantID":"t","participantAge":"t","participantGender":2,"confirmationCode":"0814093","participantFeedback":"","transferCounterbalance":false,"intermingledTrials":false,"totalTrials":16,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":30.0,"getReadyDuration":3.0,"totalExperimentTime":0.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15],"scannerTriggerTimes":[],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":5,"trialListIndex":[5],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[2.5802557468414308,0.6429104804992676,0.8444770574569702,0.5668901801109314],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[1.7903544902801514,2.5098280906677248,2.2430129051208498,2.7747111320495607],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.2381181716918947,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[0.5796310305595398,1.9484647512435914,0.5322225093841553,1.5198086500167847],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[3.1502606868743898,1.5642797946929932,2.157315254211426,3.470639228820801],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.7915866374969484,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[0.5101783275604248,0.8698663711547852,1.7315915822982789,3.9314727783203127],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.286139726638794,1.5464109182357789,2.764615535736084,1.6925956010818482],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.105663299560547,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.3652594089508057,2.6756820678710939,0.5468722581863403,2.563688039779663],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[1.71505606174469,1.817903757095337,1.5323606729507447,2.4231464862823488],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.0114264488220217,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[2.3454079627990724,1.628994345664978,2.622471332550049,1.9404361248016358],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.3495917320251467,3.0066704750061037,1.5477253198623658,2.268975019454956],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.6507680416107179,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[1.7191928625106812,0.5175107717514038,0.9547151327133179,1.4560474157333375],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[1.9470421075820923,2.232299566268921,5.127628326416016,2.07766056060791],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.3677215576171877,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[0.6713218688964844,3.6696999073028566,0.8285703659057617,1.1648404598236085],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[4.361695289611816,4.124805450439453,2.313419818878174,2.248627185821533],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.1821694374084474,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},{"x":4.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0}],"controlStateOrder":["Human","Computer"],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":60.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[0.710811972618103,1.770392656326294,0.6727994680404663,0.5692701935768127],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[2.2671661376953127,1.5308868885040284,3.6121816635131838,1.981715440750122],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":2.8000407218933107,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"GetReady","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"controlStateOrder":[],"computerAgentCorrect":false,"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":3.0,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.0,"minDwellAtReward":0.20000000298023225,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":[],"finalGoalHitPauseTime":1.7000000476837159,"hallwayFreezeTime":[],"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.5,"blankTime":0.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[],"controlStateTransitions":[]}]}